MD. SHADMAN SAKIB SIAM

Graphic Designer and Android Developer



PROFILE

I'm an Android app developer with 5+ year experience in Startups . I like computer and programming. I've gained more than 4 years of solid experience in graphic designing. I would like to work with an ambitious company that wants to rely on the best graphics designers around.



EXPERIENCE

- Associate Member **DIU Computer & Programming Club** Feb 2021 - Dec 2023
- **Graphic Design Mentor** SignoGrafix Bangladesh April 2019 - Present
- Designer **Pixel Studio** August 2022 - Present



ACHIEVEMENT AND AWARDS

- Certified Graphic Designer CodersTrust Bangladesh 2017
- Participated in Technical Session on CLI & Shell
- Dive in Android 2.0 Comprehensive Android Bootcamp
- Participated in Ethical Hacking workshop
- Programming-URL Online Judge



LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Bangla (Native)
- English (Fluent)



RESEARCH

TO-LET an app based project



CONTACT INFORMATION

- (**L**) +8801789373772
- (C) DHANMONDI 32, 1209 **DHAKA**
- M siamsakib91@gmail.com



EDUCATION

DAFFODIL INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY BSc in CSE Fall-2023



PROBLEM SOLVING

- URI
- Codeforces
- HackerRank



PROJECTS

- Bank Management System in C
- Hospital Management System in C
- Periodic Table in Java
- To-let (App & Web)
- BMI Calculator in HTML, CSS, Java Script.



TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Skills: C, C++, Python, JAVA
- Mobile Platform: Android Development.
- Graphic Design Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator.
- Web Programming: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Database management: Firebase, MySQL.
- Version Control: Git, GitHub.
- Office Tools: Excel, Word, Powerpoint, Google Docs, Sheets, Slides.



REFERENCE

Md. Hafizur Rahman Arfin Software Engineer Brain Station - 23 arfin97@gmail.com